[Music]
mdrt
is like the olympics of what we do it is
the gathering of the world's best
advisors to come and share their best
practices so that we can learn from one
another
inspire one another and become better
advisors for our clients
what mdrit represents to me is the
pinnacle of excellence
you must set a goal to become mdrt
because when you achieve it you're among
the best in the world
in the last 16 years of becoming an mdrt
member i have had the privilege of
getting to know many many mbrt members
from around the world this has kept me
going
because mdrt has become a second family
to me and i'm glad to be a part of a
prestigious association that promotes
best practices the highest level of
ethics
as well as client service being
surrounded by the best in the industry
and mdrt conferences
and learning from the best really
enables me to bring home
these best practices to my clients and
my loved ones mdrc represent
a whole person concept i want to be
successful in life
and not just in terms of business so
successful in life to me is
family time with friends having a good
health
financial security and intellectual
growth 10 years ago when i first cleared
my first
mbrt i feel that that was the only
benchmark that we should always be
striving for
so i actually played a clt provisionally
by june this year based on the revised
standard
and i want to do a cot based on the
original sentence by annotation
incidentally i was having coffee with
one of my clients during one of our
review and she suddenly held my hand and
said gene
i really would like to have an mdrt
agent so i just thought about it i said
okay i will do it for you this year
and i've never looked back since i
believe everyone should set their
standards higher each year so that we
can grow and progress
every single year you must believe in
yourself
and be consistent in everything that you
do learn to win
every single day i really encourage you
that you need to start with a belief
not just in your mind but also in your
heart focus on what you can control
focus on your purpose and your
intentions and let
that purpose and intention really offset
that fear
plan for excellence and then pray for
grace because in this pandemic it has
shown us that anything can happen
in this day and age fight to do mdrt
this year
for the kind of person you need to
become to achieve it you need to be more
disciplined you need to persevere you
need to work hard
those are the real values you get so
when you strive to do mdrt
you will be completely transformed to a
brand new person that's the real gift
that mjit gives you
i believe that all of us should set a
goal that excites us
a goal that we wake up and feel that we
want to do something about it
so i encourage all of you who have not
hit mdrt
to go for mdrt this year those who have
already hit mdrt go for cot
and even tlt my advice is find your
reason
find the how and just do it my
encouragement to you
aim high keep going don't stop believing
in yourself whatever you think
you become whatever you feel you attract
whatever you imagine
you create let's create mdit together
[Music]
you